Okay, I want you to watch this video and then I'm gonna tell you how the fine-ass Anthony fight and my book What Would the Ancestors Say?
Connect
That's physical I gotta take your soul in the ring
Because how do you plan on doing that like let's call it energy
Frequency leaving their body
Anthony Joshua exposed what colonizer results tried to hide
West African societies developed fighting systems that operated on three levels at the same time
This knowledge wasn't erased when peeps got enslaved
It's stored in muscle memory that survives everything and this worked in Haiti
They used this system defeat Napoleon the smurf in Virginia
Biafran women who were trained warriors and ran away at a rate of 142%
Fly weasels panicked and banned all of it
But Africans were smart enough to preserve disguising it into dances games songs
They weren't just preserving fighting techniques spiritual technology that is so advanced and remembering you have access to it is how you win
So in the foreword to my book what would the ancestors say I state my ultimate thesis listen up
At the time of writing this 2025 edition the world has plummeted into what I and many others describe as a spiritual war
Every aspect of living has been usurped for the goal of material wealth and dominance thus here's where the connection happens
I feel it only logical that in facing the anti-humanist efforts of our time
We must reclaim all the above
Our connection to land spirit and empathy in order to break the barriers that have been built
What i'm trying to say is that anthony is
literally
Doing that in this fight by
Connecting
Not just the fighting skills
But the spiritual grounding of his indigenous peoples the yoruba and west african to actually win in the ring
If you want to read more go check out what would the ancestors say available only at amandalandexports and amandaseals.com
But this doesn't have to be applied solely in the ring in literal terms, baby, we are in the ring
And the irony is that he was fighting somebody who is a representative a chosen and willing body
Perpetuating and carrying forth the efforts of what I named as the anti-humanist empires
Yes, there were african people that were stolen and trafficked across the oceans and disconnected from our people
from our land and from our spirituality and gods
Once we got here they further made more efforts to continue that disconnection
They did that with the native american people and putting them in boarding schools from australia to canada and the united states
There's something very real to the fact that the effort of disconnecting
Was early on seen as an integral aspect of defeating the indigenous peoples of this land and our fine
brother anthony joshua
Has shown us in real time that when you are connected
Not just in skill but in belief and in spiritual practice
You can bring these mofos to their knees
If you want to read more go check out what would the ancestors say available only at amandalandexports and amandaseals.com
when you are connected to the